All pirates searching for the treasure One Piece must brave the second half of the Grand Line.
These wild and dangerous seas are known as the New World.
Gold Roger and his crew were the only men to ever chart these waters and learn all the secrets they held.
For the rest of the pirates of the world, this has proven to be the end of the road, a graveyard of dreams.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber after eating the gum gum fruit, set sail into the New World with his faithful crew.
I'm gonna be the king of the pirates!
The first stop on Luffy's journey is Fishman Island, thousands of feet below sea level, where his crew becomes involved in a civil war.
Meeting Jinbei, they learn of the events that led to the conflict.
He tells the tale of the Fishman Pirates, the island's brave queen, and its hero, Fisher Tiger.
It's okay for you to cry!
We are nothing like those evil celestial dragons, so don't you dare act like we are.
Now watch.
No killing. Not now. Not ever. No matter how far the journey.
We are taking this girl back home!
The death of the hero! A shocking truth of Tiger!
It took a while, but we finally got an eternal pose to Koala's hometown.
Nyu! You hear that, Koala? You could go back to your family!
Um, really?
Nyu! Ha-ha-ha!
Well, aren't you pretty!
Your parents will be proud to see what a fine young lady you become!
I don't...look silly.
We got rid of those old rags of yours. You don't want them back, right?
Nyu!
You may feel awkward at first, but I promise, your mom will be happy!
I should clean!
You! You gotta break that weird habit of yours, okay?
You're just a normal girl. This isn't Marie Joie.
Ah, just let her do what she wants.
You?
The girl was traumatized. You can't expect her to stop that easily.
These things take time.
Sorry.
You should listen to Aladdin. He would know.
Yes. Because you were a slave once yourself, weren't you?
But those feelings might be better served if you killed her.
Former slave or not, she's human.
Just like the ones who owned you.
I think we've heard enough hour long.
Let me ask you a little question.
Tell me the truth.
Even though we spared your life,
I bet your parents don't give a damn about fishmen.
Humans think they're superior to everyone.
That's why there's no point in saving a so-called innocent child,
because all of them are guilty.
She'll go home and she'll learn to hate us.
It won't stop until we stop them.
Until we take them down a peg.
But you know that, right?
You've seen the way they look at us, haven't you?
The fear, the contempt in their eyes.
If it were my decision, they would all be five feet under right now.
Some humans, but hardly all of them.
I think you need to look closer.
Is that so?
I see fear, but that is not the same as contempt.
Is it because we're pirates?
Why are you so afraid of us?
Cause I...
I don't know much about you.
I've heard that before.
It's true that our only exposure to humans has been negative,
but that doesn't mean we can judge all humans the same.
Fear comes from ignorance.
Koala, let's play a game.
See if you can figure out which hand it's in.
There, okay, guess.
Um...
That one?
Nope, too bad.
Here it is.
Okay, one more try.
Alright, watch close.
Now guess.
Um... this one?
Oh, so close.
Another place.
Fuck out.
The issue looks as though.
Well and of his乱 répondre.
Look it's pretty cool that a lot.
What kind of encounter will it be?
What's interesting?
Am I striking out?
The day as the night, the moon of a royal츠,
the flame of a fallen was waiting for you.
Girl of endeavors and Frolices.
What kind of capture are lies without you?
Then, just as she started to open up to the crew,
we reached her last stop, Full Shot Island.
Her hometown at last, as promised.
This is it, Koala.
Time to bid the ship farewell.
Where's your home village?
Come on, I'll walk you to the entrance at least.
Okay.
Don't go, Koala. You can keep sailing with us.
You're a good girl, even if you're human!
Would you pull it together?
I'll tell the whole village how great you guys are!
I'll let everyone know that fishmen are nice and not scary!
I'll miss you! So long!
Thanks for helping me!
Bye! Good luck out there!
doing fun!
Look out there!
Yeah!
.
Hmm...
You think she's cute now, but she'll be a fish man hating bigots soon enough.
Orlang, you take that back.
Huh?
Jinbei.
Enough. All right?
Always so noble.
Funny. Three years ago, you weren't like this.
What's that?
Don't be a fool.
One girl telling her village that fishmen are nice isn't going to change a thing.
Just like poor Queen Otahime.
No one will listen, and no one will give a damn.
It's Koala!
She came back. Look, it's your daughter. Come and see for yourself.
It is her.
Yeah.
Hey, guys!
Hurry. Go and tell her low.
Koala!
You're home!
Mom?
I'm so glad you're back.
I miss you so much!
Mom! I love you!
This is the best day!
Hey, that's the captain of the Sun Pirates.
Fish or tiger?
Fish men are bad guys, aren't they?
I'm scared.
I'm sorry I couldn't protect you.
I know you had an awful time, but you'll be safe with me now.
Some good things happened, too.
The nobles were mean, but I also made friends.
Everyone said fish men are bad, but that's because they don't know them.
I met a whole bunch of nice fish men.
They're the ones who brought me here.
I sailed for a long time with Uncle Tiger and all his friends.
If you got to know them, you'd like them, too.
That's all it takes.
Uncle Tiger!
You can't sneak off yet!
Thanks! I'll miss you!
Take care now!
I'll never forget you, not for the rest of my life!
And I won't forget Hachi or Aladdin either.
Even if we never see each other again, we will be able to move on to the cloud.
If you're not to know them, you'll be like them, too.
Look.
If you got to know them, you'd like them, too.
That's all it takes.
Uncle Tiger!
You can't sneak off yet!
Thanks! I'll miss you.
Take care now!
I'll never forget you, not for the rest of my life!
And I won't forget Hachi or Aladdin, either!
Even if we never see each other again!
I know these things happen slowly, but by the time you grow up, I hope our people can finally get along.
Aha! There you are, Fisher Tiger of the Sun Pirates. I'm Rear Admiral Strawberry. We were informed that you might be stopping on this island.
That girl was property of the Celestial Dragons, but we're going to look the other way on that matter, at least for the time being.
That is to say, the village elders were more than willing to sell you out as long as we spared her.
Do you know why I'm here? You must, so I won't waste your time. This is rather generous, all things considered, but you're facing two charges. Assault and escape.
What the? What in the hell is going on?
It's from the same direction Boss was headed.
Surely they wouldn't attack him.
Look! Out at sea!
Two! It's the Navy! We're surrounded!
What are they doing here?
It was a damn trap! The brat was nothing but a ploy to lure us here!
They played us for fools! We show them an ounce of kindness and this happens!
See? Humans are monsters!
Those bastards!
Wait, no! It must be Tiger they want!
Hey! You guys, guard the boat! I'm gonna go save the boss!
Good! We finally agree! When you stop yapping and start throwing punches, I know you won't let me down!
I'll take that as a compliment. Let's go!
Hey, Arlong, sir! This is bad! The ship is gonna sink!
Jump in the sea!
Our ship's done for! Let's hijack one of theirs!
How is this monster still fighting back? We're plugging him full of bullets and he's just shrugging it off!
A monster? You humans think I'm a monster? We'll see!
Fire!
Did you hear that noise, Mom? It was loud!
What noise?
I was right! Boss!
Rear Admiral, sir! The Sun Pirates came to save Tiger!
I see. It's him. Yes. Team Bay!
My friends, I'm sorry.
Are you the one responsible for this?
I do it all for justice. And justice demands I crush criminals like you!
Curse you!
Do you want to die with your captain?
You're not as strong as you think, human!
We were able to rescue our boss from the Marines as planned. And although our ship was sucked during battle, Arlong was able to secure a new one from the enemy.
Then...
What?!
What do you mean you don't want a transfusion? Are you crazy? You don't have time! You're gonna die!
You've lost far too much blood! Whatever your feelings are, you must reconsider!
The boss has a very rare blood type. No one on the crew is compatible, so we need another option!
The blood they have stocked on the ship wouldn't be from fishmen. It would be... human.
So what? It should work. Humans and fishmen share the same blood. We found your type as well. So it's settled, alright?
Now just relax. You're all good.
Get away!
I would rather die than live with their blood.
I won't put that filth in my body. The blood of the bastards who tried to kill me.
Dammit, no!
I won't take their mercy. I will not owe them. I won't give in to any human! I won't!
What happened? Something changed for you to say this!
I didn't want... to tell you guys this... but I... on my last trip...
That was quite a lengthy voyage you took!
Yeah, an eventful one too.
Tell me, why are you so adamant about this? What did you see on your trip?
I saw human nature.
Soon after I started off on my journey... they captured me... in Mariejoie. They made me... I was... a damn slave!
Boss, no!
Tiger! I saw true human corruption. True depravity. I barely escaped. But then... I kept thinking about those other slaves. So I went back.
Listen to me. I lived... how I chose to. Against... Otohime's will. But... I still believe in her. I still believe that she's right.
Everyone wants peace. Humans and fishmen alike. But our generation can't bring that peace. We're bound to an ugly past. Only children like Koala, free of that history, can change the world.
Please. You can't... tell them. You... have to... hold it in. Our tragedy... and our hatred... they must die with us.
No, it's all wrong!
You heard me!
Some humans... are kind. They know. We're not so different. I know it too. And because I've met so many compassionate humans, I realize it's foolish to leave nothing but hatred as legacy when I die.
But even though my mind understands that, there is a devil in my heart that cannot forgive. That fills me with rage. My very flesh rejects them. It rejects their blood.
Despite all that I've fought for, I cannot love them. I'm sorry!
I'm sorry!
However you feel, you can work it out when this is all done. For now, I'm begging you, just live!
Listen, boss. You're a hero. Those slaves that you set free, they owe you their very lives. Please, boss, you can't die. Not like this. To every slave and every fishman, you're a symbol of hope.
Then I'm happy.
You're still not strong enough.
Damn it!
You have to step in front of your men, with your whole body. Do that. You protect them.
Huh? Why would I...
Jinbei!
If there's no one else who can challenge me, I'm the new leader of the Fishman District. Call me Tiger!
Tiger! We're all brothers now. Your blood is my blood. So I swear that I'll protect it. I'll fight for the lives of every fishman!
I swear to god3d for each other. I beg your love. I hate
to keep it on my hands. Where are you guys, haha?
No!
Fisher-Tiger's death comes as a great shock to all.
In the aftermath of his demise,
fishmen are left wondering if they can truly coexist with humans.
While Jinbei vows to uphold Tiger and Otohimi's ideals,
Arlong's resentment grows.
It's only a matter of time before the Sun Pirates face a crisis of identity.
On the next One Piece,
The Sun Pirates Split!
Jinbei versus Arlong!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!
...